Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Productions, circa 1910-1971, II.; 402 photographs
  - Oliver Smith's sketch for set of Martha, Act III, 1960?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 19, Item C19-056)
  - Martha (1961), 1961, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 19, Item C19-057)
  - Martha, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 19, Item C19-058)
  - Don Chisciotte, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Gnani (Bologna, Italy) (Box 19, Item C19-059)
  - Bodas de Sangre, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 19, Item C19-060)
  - Andrea Chenier, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 19, Item C19-061)
  - Andrea Chenier, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 19, Item C19-062)
  - Fedora, Act III, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-063)
  - Fedora, Act II, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 19, Item C19-064)
  - Alceste, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 19, Item C19-065)
  - Iphigenie en Aulide, 1950, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Levi (Florence, Italy) (Box 19, Item C19-066)
  - Iphigenie en Aulide, 1950, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 19, Item C19-067)
  - Iphigenie en Tauride, 1957?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-068)
  - Orfeo ed Euridice ballet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Leoni (Genoa, Italy) (Box 19, Item C19-069)
  - Faust, 1946, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 19, Item C19-070)
  - Romeo et Juliette, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 19, Item C19-071)
  - Romeo et Juliette?, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 19, Item C19-072)
  - Covent Garden program for Romeo et Juliette (1893), 1893, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 19, Item C19-073)
  - Giulio Cesare, Act I, scene 1a, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-074)
  - Giulio Cesare, Act I, scene 2, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-075)
  - Giulio Cesare, Act I, scene 3a, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-076)
  - Giulio Cesare, Act II, scene 1a, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-077)
  - Giulio Cesare, Act III, scene 3a, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 19, Item C19-078)
  - Jenufa, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 19, Item C19-079)
  - Jenufa, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 19, Item C19-080)
  - Pagliacci, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-001)
  - Pagliacci, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 20, Item C20-002)
  - Pagliacci, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-003)
  - Cavalleria rusticana, 1941, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-004)
  - Cavalleria rusticana, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-005)
  - Cavalleria rusticana, 1957?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-006)
  - Cavalleria rusticana, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Francesco Leoni (Genoa, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-007)
  - Puccini's Manon Lescaut at the Metropolitan Opera, 1958-1959, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-008)
  - Massenet's Manon at the Metropolitan Opera, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-009)
  - Thais, 1960?, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 20, Item C20-010)
  - Amahl and the night visitors, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-011)
  - Amelia al ballo, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-012)
  - Cosi fan tutte, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-013)
  - Cosi fan tutte, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 20, Item C20-014)
  - Cosi fan tutte, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 20, Item C20-015)
  - Cosi fan tutte, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-016)
  - Cosi fan tutte, finale, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-017)
  - Don Giovanni, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-018)
  - Don Giovanni, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-019)
  - Don Giovanni, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-020)
  - Idomoneo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-021)
  - Nozze di Figaro, Act II, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-022)
  - Nozze di Figaro, Act IV, finale, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-023)
  - Nozze di Figaro, Act III, scene 1, 1959-1960, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-024)
  - Nozze di Figaro, 1951?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-025)
  - Nozze di Figaro, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-026)
  - Nozze di Figaro, Act II, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 20, Item C20-027)
  - Nozze di Figaro, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 20, Item C20-028)
  - Nozze di Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Francesco Leoni (Genoa, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-029)
  - Nozze di Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-030)
  - Nozze di Figaro, Act II, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 20, Item C20-031)
  - Die Zauberflöte, 1957 Aug. 16, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 20, Item C20-032)
  - Die Zauberflöte, Act II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 20, Item C20-033)
  - Die Zauberflöte, 1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-034)
  - Boris Godunov, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-035)
  - Boris Godunov, Act IV, scene 1, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-036)
  - Boris Godunov, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 20, Item C20-037)
  - Boris Godunov, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 20, Item C20-038)
  - Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Stampa (Box 20, Item C20-039)
  - Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Stampa (Box 20, Item C20-040)
  - Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-041)
  - Khovanshchina, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Campagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-042)
  - Khovanshchina, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Campagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-043)
  - Khovanshchina, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Campagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-044)
  - Khovanshchina, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Campagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-045)
  - Khovanshchina, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Campagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-046)
  - Khovanshchina, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Campagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-047)
  - Les Contes d'Hoffmann, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-048)
  - La perichole, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-049)
  - La perichole, Act I, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-050)
  - La perichole, Act II, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-051)
  - La perichole, Act III, scene 1, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-052)
  - La perichole, Act III, scene 2, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-053)
  - Assassinio nella cattedrale, Act I, scene 2a, 1958-1959, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-054)
  - Assassinio nella cattedrale, Act II, scene 2a, 1958-1959, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-055)
  - Assassinio nella cattedrale, Act III, scene 3a, 1958-1959, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-056)
  - Fra Gherardo, Act I, finale, 1928?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-057)
  - La gioconda, Dance of the hours, 1952?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-058)
  - La gioconda, Act I, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 20, Item C20-059)
  - La gioconda, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 20, Item C20-060)
  - La gioconda, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-061)
  - Dialogues des Carmelites, Act I, scene 4a, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-062)
  - Dialogues des Carmelites, Act II, scene 4a, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-063)
  - Dialogues des Carmelites, Act III, scene 4a, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 20, Item C20-064)
  - Prokofiev's ballet, Romeo e Giulietta, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 20, Item C20-065)
  - War and peace, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 20, Item C20-066)
  - La boheme, Act II, 1957?, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 21, Item C21-001)
  - La boheme, Act IV, death of Mimi, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-002)
  - La boheme, Act II, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-003)
  - La fanciulla del west, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 21, Item C21-004)
  - La fanciulla del west, Act III, 1949, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-005)
  - Gianni Schicchi, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-006)
  - Gianni Schicchi, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-007)
  - Gianni Schicchi, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Fiorenza (Florence, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-008)
  - Madama Butterfly, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-009)
  - Madama Butterfly, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 21, Item C21-010)
  - Madama Butterfly, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-011)
  - Madama Butterfly, Act II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Francesco Leoni (Genoa, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-012)
  - Madama Butterfly, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Savio, Oscar (Box 21, Item C21-013)
  - Manon Lescaut, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-014)
  - Tosca, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-015)
  - Tosca, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-016)
  - Tosca, Act I, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 21, Item C21-017)
  - Tosca, Act I, Te Deum, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-018)
  - Tosca, Act II, dress rehearsal, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 21, Item C21-019)
  - Tosca, Act II, Tosca stabs Scarpia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-020)
  - Tosca, Act III, Love duet, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-021)
  - Tosca, Act III, Execution of Cavaradossi, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-022)
  - Tosca, Act III, Execution of Cavaradossi, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-023)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 21, Item C21-024)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-025)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-026)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-027)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-028)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-029)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-030)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-031)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-032)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-033)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 21, Item C21-034)
  - Turandot, Act II, scene 4, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-035)
  - Turandot, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-036)
  - Turandot, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 21, Item C21-037)
  - Turandot, Act II, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 21, Item C21-038)
  - Turandot, 1958, 1 color photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-039)
  - Turandot, Act III, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-040)
  - Turandot, Act III, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-041)
  - Turandot, Act III, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 21, Item C21-042)
  - Turandot, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 21, Item C21-043)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia, final scene, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-044)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia, Act II, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-045)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-046)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-047)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-048)
  - Il Barbiere di Siviglia, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-049)
  - La cenerentola, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Giacomelli (Venice, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-050)
  - La cenerentola, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Giacomelli (Venice, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-051)
  - Le Comte Ory, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Levi (Florence, Italy) (Box 21, Item C21-052)
  - Le Comte Ory, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 21, Item C21-053)
  - Le Comte Ory, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 21, Item C21-054)
  - Il Turco in Italia, 1957?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 21, Item C21-055)
  - Il Turco in Italia, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-056)
  - Il Turco in Italia, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-057)
  - Il Turco in Italia, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-058)
  - Il Turco in Italia, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-059)
  - Il Turco in Italia, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-060)
  - Samson et Dalila, Act II, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-061)
  - Samson et Dalila, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-062)
  - Samson et Dalila, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-063)
  - Bartered Bride, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 21, Item C21-064)
  - Die Fledermaus, Act I, 1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 21, Item C21-065)
  - Die Fledermaus, Act I, 1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-066)
  - Die Fledermaus, Act II, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-067)
  - Die Fledermaus, Act II, 1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-068)
  - Die Fledermaus, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-069)
  - Zigeunerbaron, 1959-1960, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-070)
  - Arabella, Act II, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-071)
  - Arabella, 1957 Jan. 7, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-072)
  - Arabella, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Ellinger, Karl (Box 21, Item C21-073)
  - Arabella, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Ellinger, Karl (Box 21, Item C21-074)
  - Ariadne auf Naxos, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 21, Item C21-075)
  - Der Rosenkavalier, Act I, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-076)
  - Der Rosenkavalier, presentation of the rose, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-077)
  - Der Rosenkavalier, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 21, Item C21-078)
  - Salome, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 21, Item C21-079)
  - Eugene Onegin, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-080)
  - Eugene Onegin, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 21, Item C21-081)
  - Mignon, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-082)
  - Mignon, Act II, scene 1a, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-083)
  - Mignon, Act II, scene 2a, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-084)
  - Mignon, Act III, scene 2a, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 21, Item C21-085)
  - Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-001)
  - Aida, Act II, scene 2, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 22, Item C22-002)
  - Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Levi (Florence, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-003)
  - Aida, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-004)
  - Aida, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-005)
  - Aida, Act I, scene 1a, 1960?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-006)
  - Aida, Act I, scene 2a, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-007)
  - Aida, Act II, scene 1a, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-008)
  - Aida, Act II, scene 2a, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-009)
  - Aida, Act III, 1957?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-010)
  - Aida, Act IV, scene 2a, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-011)
  - Aida, Triumphal scene, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-012)
  - Aida, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-013)
  - Aida, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Savio, Oscar (Box 22, Item C22-014)
  - Aida, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Savio, Oscar (Box 22, Item C22-015)
  - Aida, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 22, Item C22-016)
  - Aida, 1958, 1 color photograph; Irifoto (Box 22, Item C22-017)
  - Aida, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-018)
  - Aida, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 22, Item C22-019)
  - Aida, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-020)
  - Aida, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 22, Item C22-021)
  - Aida, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 22, Item C22-022)
  - Aida, curtain call, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 22, Item C22-023)
  - Aida, Act II, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-024)
  - Aida, Act II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-025)
  - Un ballo in maschera, Act I, scene 1a, 1957-1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-026)
  - Un ballo in maschera, Act I, scene 2a, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-027)
  - Un ballo in maschera, 1957-1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-028)
  - Un ballo in maschera, Act III, scene 1a, 1957-1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-029)
  - Un ballo in maschera, Act III, scene 2a, 1957-1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-030)
  - Un ballo in maschera, Act III, scene 3a, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-031)
  - Un ballo in maschera, Act I, scene 1, 1956 Feb. 17, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-032)
  - Un ballo in maschera, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-033)
  - Un ballo in maschera, 1958 Oct. 21, 1 black and white photograph; Rydberg, Enar M (Box 22, Item C22-034)
  - Don Carlos, Act II, scene 2, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 22, Item C22-035)
  - Don Carlos, Act IV, Elisabetta's prayer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 22, Item C22-036)
  - Don Carlos, Act III, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 22, Item C22-037)
  - Don Carlos, Act IV, Elisabetta's prayer, 1950?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-038)
  - Don Carlos, 1950?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-039)
  - Don Carlos, 1950?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-040)
  - Don Carlos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 22, Item C22-041)
  - Don Carlos, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Ellinger, Karl (Box 22, Item C22-042)
  - Don Carlos, Act III [i.e. IV], scene 1, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-043)
  - Ernani, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 22, Item C22-044)
  - Ernani, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 22, Item C22-045)
  - Ernani, 1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 22, Item C22-046)
  - Falstaff, Act II, 1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-047)
  - Falstaff, Act III, scene 2, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-048)
  - Falstaff, Act III, scene 1, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 22, Item C22-049)
  - La forza del destino, 1960 Feb. 1, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 22, Item C22-050)
  - La forza del destino, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-051)
  - La forza del destino, Act I, scene 3, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 22, Item C22-052)
  - La forza del destino, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Giacomelli (Venice, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-053)
  - La forza del destino, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Giacomelli (Venice, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-054)
  - La forza del destino, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Giacomelli (Venice, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-055)
  - La forza del destino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-056)
  - Macbeth, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Box 22, Item C22-057)
  - Macbeth, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 22, Item C22-058)
  - Macbeth, Act I, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 22, Item C22-059)